Jonathan Duck

Front End Developer

Austin, TX | 903-918-5728 | jduck1133@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/duck126/

Professional Summary

Former Active Duty military & Well trained Junior Web developer able to build a Web presence from the ground up -- from concept, navigation, layout, testing, as well as UX. Experience collaborating with a team of fellow developers to bring multiple Full-Stack projects into production under deadline, while maintaining code that is clear and concise. Motivated team player with the capacity to learn and adapt every single day. I would revel at the opportunity to be a part of your team!

Proficient Languages & Frameworks

- JavaScript 7
- MySQL 7
- Node 7
- Sequelize 6
- React 5
- Mongoose 7
- Express 7

MongoDB - 6

- Google Maps API 7
- Materialize CSS 8
- BootStrap CSS 8
- Git CLI 8
- Heroku 8
- Firebase 5
- Material UI 8

Professional Experience

Senior Radio Telephone Operator

2012 - 2016

United States Army

- Supervised and Instructed personnel in the operation and general maintenance of high grade communication equipment.
- Kept record and Accountability of over 500 different communication systems valued totaled over \$3,700,000 without a single occurrence of lost property.
- Provided and Oversaw high level maintenance on equipment which resulted in over 95% of all systems remaining consistently fully operational.
- Implemented the use of tactical satellites that played a crucial role in maintaining communications during 13 full scale operations.

Unmanned Aerial System Operator

2013 - 2016

United States Army

- Conducted air reconnaissance, surveillance, targeting and acquisition missions that provided the Division with vital information that attributed to the success of the missions.
- Successfully recovered Unmanned Aerial System after every flight with no loss or damage to the system valued at upwards of \$250,000.

Education

Coding Boot Camp University of Texas Austin January 2018 - July 2018

End Game

Web App that calculates center location that is closest for all users of a selected group and search for places to meet around that location.

Skills Applied: React, Material UI, Express, MongoDB, Node, Google API.

URL: https://endgame2.herokuapp.com/

EventFull

Web App built around EventBrite API and used to locate upcoming events in any city selected by the user, events are displayed on a Map along with date, location, time and event information.

Skills Applied: React, Material UI, Express, Node, Axios, React Google Maps, EventBrite API.

URL: *Under Maintenance*